如果恶魔石碑能关上地狱大门
If the demon tablet can shut the gates of hell,
天使石碑会有什么威力
what can the angel tablet do?
我不能让你带走它  迪恩
I can't let you take that, Dean.
我现在只知道要保护这块石碑
I just know that I have to protect this tablet now.
-防着娜奥米吗  -还有你
- From Naomi? - And from you.
我  你在说什么呢
From me? What are you talking about?
小卡  见鬼
Cass! Damn it.
-我叫娜奥米  -我知道你是谁
- My name is Naomi. - Oh, I know who you are.
我知道小卡离开炼狱后你对他做了什么
And I know what you did to Cass after he got out of purgatory.
卡西迪奥  他们在控制我们
They're controlling us, Castiel!
而现在卡西迪奥不知去向
And now Castiel is in the wind
兜里还揣着个氢弹
with a hydrogen bomb in his pocket.
上帝建立了一系列测试
God built a series of tests.
等你都完成了  就可以去关门了
When you've done all three, you can slam the gates.
第二道测试是什么
What's the second trial?
从地狱拯救一个无辜的灵魂
An innocent soul has to be rescued from hell
并将它送入天堂
and delivered unto heaven.
做完了
It's done.
第二个测试对你的伤害比第一个要大很多
That second trial hit you a lot harder than that first one.
他钻进了我的脑子  迪恩
He's in my head, Dean.
恐惧  躲藏
Fear, the hiding.
那样的话  他就知道我的位置
And if he's in my head, he knows where I am!
以为你能躲我一辈子吗
Thought you could elude me forever?
他不见了
He's gone.
小毛孩逃了
Little geek made a run for it.
是啊  但他会去哪
Yeah, but where?
如今
凯文  是我们  开门啊
Kevin, come on! It's us! Open up.
等死人啦
We're bleeding out here.
伙计  是我啊
Come on, man. It's me.
现在我湿了
Now it's wet me.
你忘了敲门暗号
You forgot the knock.
如果你不那么敲还制定敲门暗号做什么
What's the point of a secret knock if you don't use it?
抱歉  凯文
Sorry, Kevin.
我们拿到了
We got it.
拿到什么
Got what?
我们得到消息
Uh, we caught a tip
克劳力在到处活动
that Crowley was moving his earth-side operations,
于是我们就设了个套
so we, uh, laid ourselves an awesome trap.
也得到了回报
And it worked.
我们拿到那一半石碑了
We got the other half of the tablet.
什么
What?
守得云开见月明了  孩子
It's the light at the end of your tunnel, kid.
可别说我们没给过你什么
Don't say we never got you nothing.
天呐  真的假的
Holy crap. Are you kidding?
我们可以解开第三道测试了
We can get the third trial.
终于能知道
We can finally figure out
要如何永远把克劳力关在地狱里了
how to close the gates of hell on Crowley's ass forever.
那太好了
Sounds good to me.
那我们去把另一半的石碑找出来啊
So, we digging up the other half of that thing or what?
不用
Don't need to.
好了  机灵鬼
So, uh special k,
你继续埋头研究上帝的石头
you keep your nose to the God-stone.
我们去离这儿很远的地方整出点事端来
We're gonna drive out and make a lot of noise a long way from here,
好保证你这里的安全
keep the safeboat safe for you.
我们尽快回来
We'll be back as soon as we can, okay?
他应该没事了
I guess he's okay.
好了  我们走后锁门
All right. Don't forget to lock up after us.
三道测试
So, it's three trials.
三道测试温家兄弟就能把我关起来了
Three trials and the Winchesters get to lock the door on me.
你  假萨姆
You, fake Sam,
如果你泄露了我们的秘密
if you're gonna tip our hand,
我就只能再一次抹去凯文的短时记忆
I'll have to scrub Kevin's short-term memory again.
这样很危险  所以你注意点那些土话
And that's risky, so watch the patois in there.
土话
Patois?
俚语
Your slang.
"机灵鬼"  "上帝的石头"
"Special k," "Nose to the God-stone" --
迪恩才那么说话
That's the way Dean speaks.
萨姆说话更普通
Sam is...more basic,
更真诚
more sincere.
记住  我需要你们模仿得惟妙惟肖
Remember, I want two distinct,
各有特点
authentic characterizations.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
天生就是个导演
I was born to direct.
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第二十一集
好了
All right, here we go --
约翰・温彻斯特著名的包治百病炖鸡汤
John Winchester's famous cure-all kitchen-sink stew.
来了
There you go.
我放的辣椒够烧掉你的嘴皮子了
Enough cayenne pepper in there to burn your lips out,
就像爸爸做的那样
just like dad used to make.
还要哥哥喂你吗
You want me to do the whole, uh, airplane thing with the spoon?
你多久没吃东西了
When was the last time you ate?
-我不...  -好几天了  萨姆
- I don't - - Days, Sam.
都三天了
It's been three days.
你哪弄来的
When did you get that?
你什么时候开始发烧的
When did you start throwing off heat waves?
-来  -行了  迪恩  别这样
- Here. - Enough! Dean, please.
带血手绢  发烧  站不稳
The bloody handkerchiefs, the fever, the shaky legs --
这可不好
This is not good.
我是不好
Well, I'm not good,
除非我们能再次开始行动  继续第三道测试
and I'm not going to be good until we can start moving again,
我都不会好
until I can start the third trial.
测试  你连开助力车都休想
Trial? I wouldn't let you start a moped.
这事我们没有回头路
We're on the rails with this thing, okay,
只能一直走下去了
and the only way out of it is through it.
相信我  这我懂  你也知道
Believe me, I know, and you know how bad
我有多想把那些混蛋关起来
I want to slam the door on all those sons of bitches.
但你得让我照顾你
But you got to let me take care of you, man.
你得让我帮你恢复体力
You got to let me help you get your strength back.
这不是感冒或者发烧
This isn't a cold or a fever
还是其他什么你能照顾得了的病
or whatever it is you're supposed to feed.
这是测试的一部分
This is part of it all.
前两道测试  不只是我做的什么事
Those first two trials -- they're not just things I did.
他们对我有损害
T-they're doing something to me.
他们在改变我  迪恩
They're changing me, Dean.
凯文・谭发来新邮件
是凯文
It's Kevin.
终于有消息了
Finally.
萨姆  迪恩
Sam, Dean,
这段信息是我预先用软件和
I've set up this message with some software
远程服务器设置好的  如果我一周内
and a remote server so it'd send itself to you
没有重新设定命令  它就会自动发送给你
if I didn't reset it with a command once a week,
就是说我这周没有重设命令
which means I didn't reset it this week.
而那只有一种可能
And there's only one reason I wouldn't,
如果你正在看这个
which means if you're watching this then I --
那我肯定是死了
then I'm -- I'm dead.
我死了  你们两个混蛋
I'm dead, you bastards,
去你的  去上帝的  还有去所有人的
so screw you, screw God, and everybody in between!
我肯定是被克劳力发现了
Crowley must have gotten to me,
我只知道  这次我是逃脱不掉了
and the one thing I know is that I won't break this time.
我不知道我怎么知道  但我就是知道
I'm not sure how I know, but -- but I do.
我一直在上传我的笔记和翻译
I've been uploading all my notes and translations.
我会把链接发给你  这样你就能拿到了
I'm sending you the links so you can get all of it.
你们得自己想办法破解其余部分了
You guys are gonna have to try to figure out the rest.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道这是我该做的  但是我不能...
I know it was my job, but I -- but I couldn't...
对不起
I'm sorry.
该死
Damn it!
嗯  我知道你没见过他  基尔
Yeah. I know you haven't seen him, Keel.
谁都没见过
Nobody has.
好吧  如果你遇见盖思
All right, well, if you talk to Garth,
让他给我打电话
then just have him call in.
好
Yeah.
盖思还不见踪影吗
Garth still M.I.A.?
嗯
Yeah.
那下一位先知呢
How about the other prophets in line?
如果凯文
I mean, if Kevin is, uh...
死了  那不是应该出现下一个了吗
is dead, then won't one of them be activated?
完全没动静
Nothing. No, not a peep.
现在我们毫无线索  没有石碑
Here we are -- no lead, no tablet,
屁都没有
squat.
我们还有这些啊
Well, I mean, we got all this.
我们该把他带来的
We should have moved him here.
新墨西哥  圣达菲
我渐渐喜欢上这个了
I guess I've been acquiring the taste.
是吧  这咖啡还不差
Yeah? The coffee's not too bad here.
我还记得最初发现咖啡的时候
You know, I remember when you first discovered it.
开始煮咖啡之前  还只是嚼咖啡豆
Before you started brewing it, you'd just chew the berries.
传说是真的  这的确是跟山羊学的
Folktale is true, by the way. You learned it from the goats.
据传咖啡是牧羊人发现山羊嚼咖啡豆而情绪高涨发现的
你在路上走了很久吧
Uh, been on the road a long time, huh?
感觉好像一直都在逃跑
Feels like I've been on the run forever.
抱歉  先生
Um, I'm sorry, mister,
但你得点一些咖啡之外的东西
but you're gonna have to order more than coffee
才能继续坐在这儿
if you want to keep the table.
当然
Oh, of course. Um...
我要一份有益心脏的酒糟天麸罗
I'll have the smart-heart beer-battered tempura tempters.
没问题  就来
Of course. Coming right up.
他们靠近了
They're getting closer.
什么
What's that, chief?
我发誓  兰斯  那家伙就那么消失了
I swear to God, Lance, the guy just disappeared.
你又吸可卡因了吗  佩里
You on the crack again, Perry?
艾昂  告诉我你有好消息
Ion, tell me that you have good news.
他的计谋很聪明
He's using a clever tactic.
他利用一家叫比格森的连锁店
It's a restaurant called Biggerson's.
福罗里达  棕榈湾
人类建了几百家  几乎是完全相同的
The humans have built hundreds of them, almost exactly alike.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
他们的一致性
It's their sameness.
科罗拉多  丹佛
卡西迪奥利用它来反侦查
Castiel is using it against us.
宾夕法尼亚  匹兹堡
我们试着定位
Now, we try to orient ourselves,
但那感觉就像我们同时出现在每一个比格森餐厅
but it's as if we're in every Biggerson's at once,
俄勒冈  波特兰
被困在了量子叠加之中
trapped in a quantum superposition,
密苏里  圣路易斯
他能决定接下来去哪
now, he chooses which to go to next --
所以他占了先机
That's what's giving him the edge.
你是说你抓不到他
You're saying that you can't catch him?
实在有太多比格森餐厅了
There -- there is just so many Biggerson's.
好吧
Very well.
既然你说你不能抓到他
You say he can't be caught.
那我们就只能让他别跑了
Then we will simply have to make him stop.
又出现了  哪里都有
There it is again, every time.
这个符号  我见过
This symbol -- I know it.
凯文认为这是一种签名
Now, Kevin has it down as -- as sort of like a signature
上帝的书记员的签名
for the scribe of God.
每次梅塔特隆做
It appears every time Metatron makes one of his,
编辑笔记时都有
uh, like editor's notes.
好吧
Okay.
但我觉得我见过它
But I think I've seen it before.
那是很久之前了
I mean, it was a long time ago.
那是我在斯坦福上人文课时见到的
It was one of my, uh, humanities courses at Stanford.
斯坦福还教神之语
They taught word of God at Stanford?
不  是美国原住民艺术概览
No, uh...it was an overview of native American art.
好像是岩石画
I think it's a petroglyph.
岩什么
A petro-what, now?
这一符号源自科罗拉多一个小部落
This one belonged to a tiny tribe in Colorado,
应该说是一个宗族
more of a-a clan, really.
这里面说他们坚守了自己的片山头
It says here they held onto their scrap of mountains
而其他部落则败在白人手下
when all the other tribes fell to the white man.
这个字符是一个地域标记
Uh, so this glyph was a territorial marker.
最接近的翻译为"上帝的使者"
Closest translation -- "Messenger of God."
"上帝的使者"
"Messenger of God."
"上帝的使者"  迪恩  我们得去啊
"Messenger of God." Dean, we have to go there.
就凭一个直觉  你几乎没法行动
On that hunch? You can barely function.
我的情况只会更糟
I'm only gonna get worse.
直到我能继续做我该做的
I mean, until I get back to the real job,
直到我们弄明白第三道测试
until we find the third trial --
我们需要个先知啊
we're out of prophets!
凯文都弄不明白的我们也别想
We're not gonna figure out what Kevin couldn't!
我们该去找这个上帝的使者
I say we go to this messenger of God
毕竟是这就是他写的
who wrote it in the first place!
那你觉得这个梅塔特隆
And you think that this Metatron
跟一群印第安人藏在深山老林里吗
is hiding out in the mountains with a bunch of indians?
没错
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
但你不该说印第安人
You're not -- you're not really supposed to say "Indians."
那是...我们该走了
It's... we should go.
你真有病
You are delirious.
缅因州  班戈
内布拉斯加州  林肯
内华达  里诺
亚利桑那州  图森
新墨西哥州  圣达非
你得停下
You have to stop.
他们说你得停下
They said you have to stop.
不
No.
-他们说你得停下  -不
- They said you have to stop. - No.
你得停下
You have to stop.
不要
No.
你得停下
You have to stop.
他们说你得停下
They said you have to stop.
你得停下
You have to stop.
科罗拉多州  34号公路
好地方
Nice place.
早上好
Morning. Hi.
我们想要开间房
Uh, we'd like a room.
住这里  谢谢
Here, please.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
听到什么
Hear what?
他得了流感
He has the flu.
你得停下
You have to stop.
你得停下  他们说你
You have to stop. They said you --
都听不清自己在想什么了
Can't hear myself think.
我们本应照顾他们  而不是谋杀他们
We were supposed to be their shepherds, not their murderers.
并不总是如此  天使
Not always, angel.
不久之前在埃及
There was that day back in Egypt not so long ago
我们杀死了每一个头胎婴儿
where we slew every firstborn infant
因为他们的门上没有撒上羊羔血
whose door wasn't splashed with lamb's blood,
那只是公关
and that was just P.R.
我当时不在
Well, I wasn't there.
你在
Oh, you were there.
你只是不记得了
You just don't remember it.
有多少次
How -- how many times
你钻进我的脑袋  给我彻底洗脑
have you torn into my head and washed it clean?
坦白说  太多太多次了
Frankly, too damn many.
你是著名的捣蛋鬼
You're the famous spanner in the works.
老实说  我觉得你下线的时候就没造好
Honestly, I think you came off the line with a crack in your chassis.
你从不按吩咐做事
You have never done what you were told,
总要自我发挥一下
not completely.
你连死都死不好  是吧
You don't even die right, do you?
天使之碑在哪  卡西迪奥
Where is the angel tablet, Castiel?
用我一个好朋友的话来说
In the words of a... good friend,
咬我啊
bite me.
我们会的
Oh, we'll bite.
别担心
Don't worry.
去  搜遍每个比格森
Go. Search all these...Biggerson's.
他一定在这一路上藏了起来
He must have hidden it along the way.
我看字都困难
I can barely see.
我需要食物
I need food.
好吧  烤肋排  土豆泥
All right. Uh, barbecue ribs, mashed potatoes.
蒜味土豆泥
Garlic mashed potatoeat.
蒜味土豆泥  有生菜幼叶的凉拌蔬菜
Garlic mashed potatoes, mixed greens with baby lettuce,
玉米面包  还有泰式炒河粉
cornbread, and, uh, Pad Thai.
盖思说小镇另一边有一个很不错的地方
Garth says there's a good little place on the other side of town.
管他呢  这孩子一直很努力
What the hell? Kid's been working hard.
这些人还挺不错的
Those guys aren't half bad.
是啊  您很有眼光
No, sir. You chose well.
当然  要不是我得统筹全局
Of course, if I wasn't running everything,
我就自己上阵扮迪恩了
I could have played Dean myself.
您扮迪恩一定很像  先生
Oh, you would have made a great Dean, sir.
这里就是一般的旅游圣地
Regular tourist mecca we got here.
我们是这里唯一的客人
We're the only guests in this whole place.
上一次登记入住时间是06年了
Last entry in the registry was in '06.
你记得那次
Hey, you remember when, uh...
爸爸带我俩坐骡车去
when dad took us to the bottom of the Grand Canyon on that
大峡谷谷底吗
pack-mule ride?
什么
The what?
你的
And your, uh --
你的骡子一直在放屁
your mule kept farting,
一刻不定  像刮大风一样
just letting go,  like gale force.
老弟  你那时才四岁
Dude, you were like four years old.
我都不怎么记得
I barely remember that.
你骑着屁屁驴
You rode a farty donkey.
好吧  我去查一下
Okay, uh, I'm gonna go check out
两河旅游博物馆和贸易站
the two Rivers travel museum and trading post.
好  好
Yeah, yeah!
我要...我要...
I'm gonna -- I'm gonna, um --
我要跟踪旅馆经理
I'm gonna follow the hotel manager,
愁容博士
D-Dr. Scowley-scowl.
他就像是《史酷比》里的反派角色
He's like a villain from "Scooby-doo."
《史酷比》: 六十年代美国卡通片
不  小大人
No, hey, uh, little big man,
你应该好好休息
you should get some rest.
好  这样也行
Yeah, I can do that, too.
两河部落的人
The people of the two rivers tribe
几世纪之前来到这片土地
came to this land centuries ago,
这里艰苦多石
a land that was harsh and stony.
但是他们强大的领导者
But their mighty leader
告诉他的人民他们必须留在这里
told his people that they must stay here.
他声称  这是大神神圣的信使
He claimed that this was the home on earth
在地球的家
of the Great Spirits' sacred messenger
如果他们能提供贡品
and that if they'd made offerings,
他们就会受到恩泽
Their blessings would be many.
他们的贡品是什么
What were the offerings? Huh?
大神神圣的信使要了什么
Uh, what did the Great Spirit'' sacred messenger ask for?
故事
Stories.
他让人们给他讲故事
He asked the people to tell him stories.
我想我知道恩泽是什么了
I bet I know what the blessings were.
萨姆
Sam?
我到处都找了  不在那里
I've been all over them. It's not there.
为什么
Why?
你为什么这么做
Why are you doing this?
让我们把石碑放回它该在的地方
Let us put the tablet back where it should be.
我得保护它
I need to protect it.
不让天使拿到吗
From the angels?
不让任何人拿到
From all of us.
你是不见棺材不掉泪了  是吗
I'm just going to have to pull you apart, aren't I?
娜奥米  亲爱的
Naomi, darling.
想我了吗
Miss me?
-走开  见鬼  -别紧张
- Get off! What the hell?! - Take it easy, man.
天
God!
别紧张  别紧...
Take it easy. Take it --
发现你躺在地板上  昏了过去
Found you on the floor, passed out.
你的体温都41.7度了
Your temperature was 107.
我必须得让你退烧  否则你就完蛋了
I had to force it down or you were toast.
他在这里  迪恩  梅塔特隆在这里
He's here, Dean. The Metatron is here.
我知道  我能听到他
I know it. I can hear him.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我只知道  不知为什么我和它相通
All I know is that I'm connected to it somehow.
怎么  你和它有联系  像先知那样
What, like you got a link to him, like a prophet?
我不知道
I don't know!
我只知道他在这里  梅塔特隆在这里
I just know he's here. The Metatron is here.
好吧  这里哪里
Okay. Here where?
我能指给你看
I can show you.
那个经理  他在给他寄书
The manager -- he was delivering books to him.
-书吗  -书
- Books? - Books.
精装的  平装本  小说  书
Hard-covers, paperbacks, novels -- books.
故事
Stories.
你喜欢吗
Do you like it?
我让我研发部的人融了一把天使之刃
I had my R&D people melt down one of your angel blades,
制成子弹  似乎效果不错
cast it into bullets. Seems to do the trick.
你好大胆子
How dare you.
我是你遇见的最大胆的恶魔  亲爱的
I am the daringest devil you've ever met, love.
我们之前也这样交过手  不是吗
We've been here before, haven't we?
看谁先眨眼
Let's see who blinks first.
你好啊  小卡
Hi, Cass.
对  小卡
That's right, Cass.
我收买了一个天使
I got me an angel on the payroll.
近来世界就是这样的
It's that kind of universe these days.
带上他跟我走
Now grab him and follow me.
孩子  你没事吧
Hey, kid, you okay?
我不行
I can't, all right?
石头中的裂缝
It's the break in the stone.
有重要信息  我解不出来
There's key writing. I-I can't make it out.
你们俩说得对
You guys were right.
我的确需要另一半石碑才能破译
I-I do need the other half of the tablet to get the trial.
它离这里不远
It's not too far from here.
好极了  石碑在哪
Awesome. Uh, well, what's the 10-20?
只想暂时放下主要行动  偷个闲
Just wanted to take a moment away from the main action...
和我的老生意伙伴聊聊天
...to chat with my old business partner.
我想你暂时还不会死
I assume you won't die just yet.
内脏出血  很久很痛
Takes a painful long time to bleed out from the gut.
克劳力  你想做什么就做什么
You can do whatever you want, Crowley.
我绝对不会告诉你我把石碑埋在哪里了
I will never tell you where I buried the tablet.
我知道  小卡
I know, Cass.
我知道
I know.
幸好
Luckily...
我觉得你不用告诉我
I don't believe you have to.
我这位身价昂贵的朋友
I've been getting regular updates
会定期告诉我新的消息
from my expensive friend here.
娜奥米应该一开始就抓住你的
Naomi should have caught you out of the gate,
毕竟最近她一直在你的脑袋里面转悠
seeing as lately she's been knuckles deep in that melon of yours.
她认为你碰到了石碑
She thinks that your touching the tablet
打破了她的咒语  是吗
has broken her spell over you. Hmm?
石碑本就不该被天使拿走
The tablets weren't meant for the angels,
也不是给你的
and they weren't meant for you.
她有太多的事要处理
She's got a lot on her plate,
也不怪不得没想到这点
so you can't fault her for missing it.
我自思自忖  "我啊
I was thinking to myself, "Self,
如果小卡摸了石碑就能摆脱她
"If Cass got away from her by touching the tablet,
为什么他不一直摸着石碑呢"
why would he ever stop touching the tablet?"
然后我又想
And then I thought to myself,
"我啊  他就是一直都摸着石碑  对吗"
"Self...he hasn't stopped touching the tablet, now, has he?"
你真好  真好啊
Oh, you're a pip, you are.
怎么了
What?
我是王
This is the King.
那孩子告诉我们另一半在哪了
The kid told us where the other half was,
但并不在这儿
but it...wasn't.
该死的耍我们
Dab of crap tricked us,
把我们送进了猎人陷阱
sent us into some kind of hunter mousetrap.
蠢货  你们这是在拖我后腿
You jackasses. You're ruining my streak!
看好他
Watch him.
我就回来
I'll be right back.
我应该带你去急诊室的
I should be taking you to the E.R.
他们什么都帮不了我
They can't do anything for me.
你知道吗  我开始回忆起一些事了
You know, I've been remembering things --
都是琐事  记得很清
Little things so clearly.
什么  骑驴吗
What? Donkey rides?
你曾读书给我听  在我还小
You used to read to me, um, when I was little --
真的很小的时候  读那本
I-I mean really little, from -- from that old, uh
《经典名著漫画》
"Classics illustrated" Comic book.
-你记得吗  -不记得
- You remember that? - No.
《圆桌骑士》
"Knights of the round table."
亚瑟王所有的骑士
Had all of King Arthur's knights,
他们都在设法取得圣杯
and they were all on the quest for the Holy Grail.
我记得看到一幅加拉哈德骑士的图
And I remember looking at this picture of Sir Galahad,
他跪着
and -- and -- and he was kneeling,
一束光照在他脸上
and -- and light streaming over his face.
我记得  我在想
And I remember... thinking, um,
我绝对不可能像那样去追寻
I could never go on a quest like that...
因为我不纯净
...because I'm not clean.
我还只是个小孩子
I mean, I-I was just a little kid.
也许我早就知道
You think maybe I knew,
在内心深处
I mean, deep down, that...
我知道我体内有恶魔的血
I had... demon blood in me
很邪恶  所以我
and about the evil of it and that I...
不纯净
wasn't pure?
萨姆  那不是你的错
Sam, it's not your fault.
现在这不重要了
It doesn't matter anymore,
因为这些测试
because these trials...
它们在净化我
...they're purifying me.
他们之前在这里  那些书  那些盒子
They were here, the -- the -- the books, the boxes!
不见了
They -- they're gone.
你们是谁
Who are you?
梅塔特隆
Metatron?
这是梅塔特隆  这是梅塔特隆
This is Metatron? This is Metatron?
坐下
Sit down.
谁派你们来的
Who sent you?
我们自己来的
We came on our own.
我们是温家兄弟
We're the Winchesters.
我是迪恩  他是萨姆
I'm Dean. This is Sam.
你们是米迦勒的手下
You work for Michael?
还是路西法
Or Lucifer?
什么  难道你没听说过我们
What, you really haven't heard of us?
你算是个什么天使啊
What kind of angel are you?
我们是温家双煞
W-we're the freaking Winchesters.
到什么时候算是个头
How -- how far can this go?
闭嘴
Shh. Shut up.
艾昂
Ion...
我们要放任到什么地步
How far can we let it all drop?
这个重担是留给我们的
This charge was left to us.
这是我们的使命
It's our mission.
你真的知道我们的使命吗
Do you even know what the mission was?
我们的脑子都被他们侵入过
They've been in all our heads.
我们可不是机器  任由他们摆布
We aren't machines for them to program and reprogram.
事情不该是这样的
That wasn't what this was meant to be.
管他呢
Nothing matters.
你大错特错  兄弟
You are so wrong, brother.
这很重要
It all matters.
小屁孩
You little prat.
玩得爽吧
You having fun yet?
去你的
Screw you.
我没看错吧
Am I seeing this?
你是怎么发现的
How did you figure it out?
他们忘了敲门暗号时我就发现了
It started when they forgot the secret knock.
但真正让我确定的是他们的举止
But really, it -- it was the way they acted.
就算在兴头上  萨姆和迪恩
I don't think on their best day Sam and Dean
也不会跑到镇上给我买烤肉吃
would go into town and get me a barbecue dinner,
况且冰箱里还有剩的墨西哥卷呢
n-not when there are leftover burritos in the fridge.
所以说
So...
我家的小鬼们还太有礼貌了
My Demons were too polite?
是啊
Yeah.
真他妈的
Well, I'll be a son of a whore.
米迦勒和路西法...
Michael and Lucifer --
这几个家伙都已经下油锅了
T-those -- those dudes are in the deep fryer.
是啊  是被我们丢进去的
Yeah. We put them there ourselves.
那加百列和拉斐尔呢
What about Gabriel and Raphael?
死了
Dead.
你是真不知道啊
You really don't know this?
我一直很小心
I've been very careful.
喂  你能...
Hey, can you --
你能把它关掉吗
Can you turn that down?
关掉什么
Turn what down?
你在共鸣
You're resonating.
共鸣  什么意思  什么叫共鸣
Resonating? What -- what do you mean, resonating?
你正在接受测试
You've undertaken the trials.
你在做测试呢吧
You're trying to pull one of the great levers, aren't you?
而且你做了不少了
You're pretty far along, too.
你走到这一步  就会开始与圣语共鸣
You get that far along, you start resonating with the word
或者与其物质层面上的源头共鸣
or with its source on the material plane --
也就是我
with me.
你说你很小心  怎么个小心法
You said you were being careful. Careful how?
我跟他们不是一类
I'm not one of them.
我不是大天使
I'm not an archangel.
我就是个普通天使
I'm really more run-of-the-mill.
在上帝选我记录神之语前
I worked in the secretarial pool
我就是个小秘书
before god chose me to take down the word.
反正他对他的工作非常忧虑
Anyway, he seemed very worried about his work,
担心他离开之后心血不保
what would happen to it when he left,
所以他让我记录下指示
so he had me write down instructions.
然后就消失了
Then he was gone.
此后...
After that...
大天使们接管了
The archangels took over.
他们哭天喊地
They cried, and they wailed.
他们只想要天父回来  我们都想
They wanted their father back. I mean, we all did.
但后来呢  他们开始密谋
But then -- then they started to scheme.
大天使们认为  既然他们成了没爹的苦孩子
The archangels decided if they couldn't have dad,
那就自己掌管整个宇宙吧
they'd take over the universe themselves.
但是没了神之语
But they couldn't do anything that big
他们成不了如此大业
without the word of god.
所以我慢慢意识到
So I began to realize
他们有天可能会发现
maybe they would realize...
他们需要我
they needed me.
所以你为此很担心
So, you get a ruffle in your feathers
决定从此躲起来
and just decide to disappear,
打算一辈子把头埋在沙子里
go stick your head in the sand forever?
你不知道外面世界都发生了什么
You have no idea what's been going on out there?
不知道
Nope.
就是这么打算的
That's the whole point.
你们这些下面的卫戍兵
You soldiers down in the garrison --
至少他们让你相信了谎言
At least they let you believe the lie.
上面的  为娜奥米干活儿  秘密行动
Upstairs, working for Naomi, working in intelligence,
别无选择  只能活在肮脏之中
we had no option but to live in the dirt.
她从未对我进行完全重启  我知道的太多了
She never reset me completely. I always knew too much.
我得完成我的任务
I had to -- I had to do my job.
艾昂
Ion...
闭嘴
Shut up!
那么你一直窝在这里  或者是个小木屋
So you have been holed up here or -- or -- or in a wigwam
或者在什么洞里
or before that, in some cave,
听故事  读小说
listening to stories, reading books?
大有看头哦
And it was something to watch.
你们人类带到k的世界中的
What you brought to his earth --
那些重罪  谋杀
all the mayhem, the murder,
上帝的人类
just the raw,
你们原始而狂野的创造
wild invention of god's naked apes --
真让人大开眼界
It was mind-blowing.
但说实在的
But really, really...
真正有趣的是你们所讲的故事
It was your storytelling.
这是真正的自由意志之花
That is the true flower of free will,
至少是你们目前能掌握的自由意志
at least as you've mastered it so far.
当你们创造故事时  你们就是上帝
When you create stories, you become gods
虽然是在你们自己一个微小复杂的范围内
of tiny, intricate dimensions unto themselves.
一花一世界啊
So many worlds.
我读过...
I have read...
我已经尽一个天使所能去读了
...as much as it's possible for an angel to read,
而我还是没能全部读完
and I haven't caught up.
知道吗
You know what?
开枪吧
Pull the freaking trigger.
什么
What?
-开枪吧  -萨姆
- Pull the freaking trigger... - Sam.
你这个胆小的垃圾
you cowardly piece of garbage.
这么长时间  你一直躲在这儿
All the time you've been hiding here,
你读到了多少苦难
how much suffering have you read over?
人类在受苦
Humanity's suffering.
又有多少是出自你们族类之手
And how much of it has been at the hands of your kind?!
你想要听故事
You want a story?
凯文・谭的故事怎么样
Try Kevin Tran's story.
他只是个孩子
He was just a kid.
一个成绩优异的好孩子
He was a good, straight-"A" kid,
然后他被卷进了这些天使的鬼事
and then he got sucked in to all of this -- this angel crap
变成了神之语的先知  你的先知
and became a prophet of the word of god -- your prophet.
而你应该照应他的  但你没有
And you should have been looking out for him, but no!
你在这里龟缩着  读书
Instead, you're here, holed up, reading books.
现在他死了  就因为你
He's dead now because of you.
你知道温彻斯特兄弟
You know the Winchesters
准备进行第三项测试了吧
are up to the third trial?
他们打算关掉地狱之门
You know they're gonna shut the door on hell?
我一点也不担心  孩子
I'm not worried, kid.
你不知道恶魔石碑上写了些什么
You have no idea what's on this demon tablet,
以及能从这上获取的力量
and the power you could have gotten with this
如果你没像被砍了头的小鸡一样乱跑的话
if you weren't running around like a chicken with his head cut off.
你以为我是来逼你开口的
You think I can't make you tell?
我知道你办不到  虽然你想
I know you can't, and you do, too.
知道吗
You know what?
我已经赢了
I've already won.
我有天使石碑  小混蛋
I have the angel tablet, you little smudge.
我已经有了计划安排
And I got deals and plans up the jacksie.
我...
And I don't...
不需要...你
need...you!
这就行了
Is that it?
他还好吗
Is he good?
给他点时间
Give him a minute.
你怎么通过克劳力的天使防卫咒的
How did you get past Crowley's angel warding?
我是神的书记员  我把咒语抹去了
I'm the scribe of god. I erased it.
但你看见了  是吧
But you saw, right?
你现在知道都发生了什么
I mean, you -- you're caught up on everything that's been going on,
这么久以来你的同胞对人类做的各种事
all the crap that your brethren's been doing to humanity all this time?
我救了这个男孩  不是吗
I saved the boy, didn't I?
但你要加入我们吗
But are you in? With us, I mean.
你真的想关闭地狱之门
You really intend on closing the doors of hell?
应该这么做  不是吗
Seems like the thing to do, don't it?
这是你的选择
It's your choice.
归根结底都是这个
And that's what this has all been about --
你们人类的选择
the choices your kind make.
但你得权衡这个选择
But you're gonna have to weigh that choice.
问问你自己"这么做的代价是什么"
Ask yourself, "What is it going to take to do this,"
以及"完成后世界会变成什么样"
And, "What will the world be like after it's done?"
迪恩
Dean?
Dean?!
凯文
Kevin?
我们以为失去你了呢  孩子
We thought we lost you, kiddo.
我没事
I'm good.
石碑的另一半  我拿到了
Second half of the tablet, and I got it.
第三项测试
Third trial.
我没告诉克劳力
I didn't tell Crowley.
是什么
So what is it?
治愈一个恶魔
To cure a demon.
是的
Yeah.
你是谁
Who are you?
治愈一个恶魔
Cure a demon?
好吧  先不说我完全不明白那是什么意思
Okay, ignoring the fact that I have no idea what that actually means,
如果我们这么做  你会好起来的  是吧
if we -- if we do this, you get better, right?
你不会再咳嗽得像是要把肺咳出来
I mean, you'll stop trying to cough up a lung
也不会撞上家具了
and -- and -- and bumping into furniture?
我感觉好多了  是的
I feel better, yeah,
有了前进的方向
uh, just having a direction to move in.
很好
Well, good,
我们要做的事貌似不简单
'cause where we're headed doesn't sound like a picnic.
但我们有目标了
But we're heading somewhere.
向结局前进
The end.
小卡
Cass?!
来帮帮忙
A little help here.